Manchester Evening Herald Photograph Collection
Vernon Historical Society
- Inventory
  - Frank's Market-Winner of Stamps Contest, 4/4/1974; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.414)
  - Tri City Plaza-Vernon, 05/??/74; Topics: Businesses; Vernon Circle (Box 3, Folder MH.415)
  - Senior Citizen of the Year-Vernon, 06/??/74; Topics: Senior Citizens (Box 3, Folder MH.416)
  - Vernon Town Hall-Rockville, 06/??/74; Topics: Town Government; Rockville Redevelopment (Box 3, Folder MH.417)
  - St Bernard's Church-Variety Show-Rockville, 06/??/74; Topics: Churches; Entertainment (Box 3, Folder MH.418)
  - Vincent H. Shaheen,Pres of Vincent & Thayer Advertising Agency, 6/26/1974; Names: Vincent H. Shaheen| Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.419)
  - Mr. & Mrs. Frank Husarik-5th Anniversary, 7/1/1974; Names: Frank Husarik| Topics: Marriage & Family (Box 3, Folder MH.420)
  - Steak Out Motel, progress photo-Vernon, 08/??/74; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.421)
  - Head Start-Vernon, 08/??/74; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 3, Folder MH.422)
  - SOS Program-Vernon Elementary-Vernon, 8/8/1974; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 3, Folder MH.423)
  - Day Care Center-2nd Birthday Party-Vernon, 8/16/1974; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 3, Folder MH.424)
  - Furniture Galleries-Vernon, 8/27/1974; Topics: Businesses (Box 3, Folder MH.425)
  - Thomas J. Wolff elected Pres. Of Million Dollar Round Table, 9/25/1974; Names: Thomas Wolff (Box 3, Folder MH.426)
  - Robert Houley-Vernon, 10/9/1974; Names: Robert Houley (Box 3, Folder MH.427)
  - Gerry O'Connell, Politics-Vernon, 10/10/1974; Names: Gerry O'Connell| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 3, Folder MH.428)
  - Sam Hellieu (?) Politics, 10/10/1974; Names: Sam Hellieu| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 3, Folder MH.429)
  - Robert Houley-Vernon, 10/14/1974; Names: Robert Houley| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 3, Folder MH.430)
  - Rockville Hospital Childrens' Ward-Rockville, 10/16/1974; Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 3, Folder MH.431)
  - Lake Street School Snake Pictures-Vernon, 10/22/1974; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 3, Folder MH.432)
  - Dorothy Miller's daughter-political campaign for Rorabach, 10/24/1974; Names: Dorothy Miller's Daughter| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 3, Folder MH.433)
  - Robert Houley-Campaigning for office, 10/30/1974; Names: Robert Houley| Topics: Politics & Elections; Clipping (Box 3, Folder MH.434)
  - Northeast School Music & Reading Program-Rockville, 11/??/74; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 3, Folder MH.435)
  - Rockville Hospital Auxillary Award-Rockville, 11/??/74; Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 3, Folder MH.436)
  - Author Luncheon-Vernon Jr. Women's Club-Vernon, 11/??/74; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.437)
  - Claire West-Vernon Jr. Women's Club-Vernon, 11?//?74; Names: Claire West| Topics: Social Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.438)
  - Village Gallery-Talcottville, 11/1/1974; Topics: Businesses; Talcottville (Box 3, Folder MH.439)
  - Election-Vernon, 11/6/1974; Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 3, Folder MH.440)
  - The Miracle Worker at VCMS-Vernon, 11/7/1974; Topics: Schools & Education; Entertainment (Box 3, Folder MH.441)
  - YNK Recipe Bev Burton,115 Taylor Street,Talcottville, 11/21/1974; Names: Bev Burton| Topics: Talcottville (Box 3, Folder MH.442)
  - Joyce Oliphant Junior Miss Contest-Vernon, 11/25/1974; Names: Joyce Oliphant| Topics: Social Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.443)
  - Liason Group Planting, 11/28/1974; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.444)
  - Vernon 1st Grade Thanksgiving (prep and dinner)-Vernon, 11/29/1974; Topics: Schools & Education; Holidays (Box 3, Folder MH.445)
  - Lake Street School-Glass blower-Vernon, 12/??/74; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 3, Folder MH.446)
  - Center Road School-Vernon, 12/??/74; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 3, Folder MH.447)
  - Young Irish Step Dancers at Convalescent Home-Vernon, 12/14/1974; Topics: Entertainment; Senior Citizens (Box 3, Folder MH.448)
  - James M. Troy, 1/16/1975; Names: James M. Troy (Box 3, Folder MH.449)
  - Roy MacDonald Jaycee Award-Vernon, 1/22/1975; Names: Roy MacDonald| Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.450)
  - Lake Street School Parade of Presidents-Vernon, 02/??/75; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 3, Folder MH.451)
  - Penny Ryder, 03/??/75; Names: Penny Rider (Box 3, Folder MH.452)
  - Barbara Cox, 3/6/1975; Names: Barbara Cox (Box 3, Folder MH.453)
  - Manchester Herald vs. Journal Inquirer for Cancer (Baseball game), 4/10/1975; Topics: Recreation (Box 3, Folder MH.454)
  - Dr. Moshe Paranov at RHS Band (also on 6/14/75), 5/22/1975; Names: Dr. Moshe Paranov| Topics: RHS (Box 3, Folder MH.455)
  - Judy Moakler-Vernon, 5/30/1975; Names: Judy Moakler (Box 3, Folder MH.456)
  - Northeast School student working with a speech teacher, 06/??/75; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 3, Folder MH.457)
  - Lake Street School Dog Demonstration-Vernon, 06/??/75; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 3, Folder MH.458)
  - Vernon Elementary Bicentennial meal-Vernon, 06/??/75; Topics: Schools & Education; National Events (Box 3, Folder MH.459)
  - Community Craftsmen CO-OP-Vernon, 06/??/75; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.460)
  - Lake Street School-Bicycle Parade-Vernon, 06/??/75; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 3, Folder MH.461)
  - Vernon-Rockville Quilt-Vernon, 6/5/1975; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 3, Folder MH.462)
  - Girls Athletic Award-Vernon, 6/6/1975; Topics: Recreation (Box 3, Folder MH.463)
  - Rockville High School-Construction-Rockville, 6/17/1975; Topics: RHS (Box 3, Folder MH.464)
  - John J. Carter-elected Pres. of NE Knitted Outerwear Assn., 7/5/1975; Names: John J. Carter| Topics: Businesses; Clipping (Box 3, Folder MH.465)
  - Congressman Chris Dodd-Vernon, 7/8/1975; Names: Chris Dodd| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 3, Folder MH.466)
  - Head Start Program-Vernon, 7/25/1975; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 3, Folder MH.467)
  - Northeast School Herb Garden-Vernon, 7/31/1975; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 3, Folder MH.468)
  - Railroad tracks for Rockville line above I-86 (Now 84), 8/8/1975; Topics: Transportation (Box 3, Folder MH.469)
  - Tolland County 4-H Fair-Vernon, 8/25/1975; Topics: Farming (Box 3, Folder MH.470)
  - Jaycees-gift to Rockville General Hospital, 8/27/1975; Topics: Rockville Hospital; Civic Organizations (Box 4, Folder MH.471)
  - Church Fire -Lutheran Church, Village Street-Rockville, 8/28/1975; Topics: Fire Dept.; Churches (Box 4, Folder MH.472)
  - Harvesting Corn-Vernon, 9/3/1975; Topics: Farming (Box 4, Folder MH.473)
  - Rockville Hospital Drive (Mason-Eden-Wolfanger), 9/11/1975; Names: Mason, Eden & Wolfagner| Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 4, Folder MH.474)
  - Mrs. Frances Grimes and Gov. Ella Grasso-Vernon, 9/12/1975; Names: Grimes & Grasso (Box 4, Folder MH.475)
  - Bicentennial games-Vernon, 9/15/1975; Topics: Recreation; National Events (Box 4, Folder MH.476)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution display at Ladd & Hall Furniture-Rockville, 9/19/1975; Topics: Businesses; Civic Organizations; National Events (Box 4, Folder MH.477)
  - Exchange Club Auction-Vernon, 9/23/1975; Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 4, Folder MH.478)
  - Bicentennial Event-Vernon, 9/23/1975; Topics: National Events (Box 4, Folder MH.479)
  - Suburban Women's Club Bicentennial Cookbook-Vernon, 9/23/1975; Topics: National Events (Box 4, Folder MH.480)
  - Technology in a school-Vernon, 9/27/1975; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 4, Folder MH.481)
  - Bruce A. Wilson,26 Risley Rd, VP of CT Bus & Industry Assn-Vernon, 10/22/1975; Names: Bruce A. Wilson (Box 4, Folder MH.482)
  - Vernon Depot Railroad track fight-Vernon, 10/24/1975; Topics: Transportation (Box 4, Folder MH.483)
  - Three students at Board Meeting-Vernon, 10/29/1975; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 4, Folder MH.484)
  - Senior Citizens' Bus-Vernon, 11/4/1975; Topics: Senior Citizens (Box 4, Folder MH.485)
  - Stop and Shop Opens-Vernon, 11/4/1975; Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.486)
  - Thomas Benoit elected Mayor-Vernon, 11/5/1975; Names: Thomas Benoit| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.487)
  - Connie Kelly's Bicentennial books at Center Rd School-Vernon, 11/7/1975; Names: Connie Kelly| Topics: Schools & Education; National Events (Box 4, Folder MH.488)
  - Mildred Lisk's artwork-Vernon, 11/13/1975; Names: Mildred Lisk| Topics: Arts (Box 4, Folder MH.489)
  - Lois Mulnite-Tolland City Art Assn-Vernon, 11/13/1975; Names: Lois Mulnite| Topics: Arts (Box 4, Folder MH.490)
  - Rockville Library new reading tool-Rockville, 11/17/1975; Topics: Rockville Library (Box 4, Folder MH.491)
  - Mrs. Ruth Lehman-RGH-Rockville, 11/17/1975; Names: Ruth Lehman| Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 4, Folder MH.492)
  - Edward C. Grazianni, Atty-Rockville, 11/20/1975; Names: Edward C. Grazianni| Topics: Law and Lawyers (Box 4, Folder MH.493)
  - David H. Rivera, Atty-Rockville, 11/20/1975; Names: David H. Rivera| Topics: Law and Lawyers (Box 4, Folder MH.494)
  - Pilgrim Kids-Vernon, 11/26/1975; Topics: Schools & Education; Holidays (Box 4, Folder MH.495)
  - Four boys & four Tonsilectomies-Vernon, 12/11/1975; Topics: Public Health (Box 4, Folder MH.496)
  - Center Rd School Christmas Window-Vernon, 12/18/1975; Topics: Schools & Education; Holidays (Box 4, Folder MH.497)
  - Thrifty's Building (corner Merline & Talcottville Rd)-Vernon, 12/29/1975; Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.498)
  - Memorial Builder-Ladder work-Rockville, 1/15/1976; Topics: Landmarks (Box 4, Folder MH.499)
  - Nancy Greenfield-Rainbow Girl-Vernon, 2/23/1976; Names: Nancy Greenfield| Topics: Social Organizations (Box 4, Folder MH.500)
  - Joan Zawistowski,Driggs Rd,Vernon National Bank-Vernon, 3/5/1976; Names: Joan Zawistowski| Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.501)
  - John T. Guldan,95 Jonathan Dr, Aetna Life & Casualty-Vernon, 3/12/1976; Names: John T. Guldan (Box 4, Folder MH.502)
  - Terry A. Piazza,Tolland,Vernon National Bank-Vernon, 3/24/1976; Names: Terry A. Piazza| Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.503)
  - Raymond Ramsdell,Superintendent of Schools for over 30 years-Vernon, 3/26/1976; Names: Raymond Ramsdell| Topics: Schools & Education (Box 4, Folder MH.504)
  - Ronald J. Ostafin,Vernon Society for Savings-Vernon, 5/5/1976; Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.505)
  - James W. Ashe-Savings Bank of Tolland-Vernon, 5/7/1976; Names: James W. Ashe| Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.506)
  - Alma S. Skipper, Vernon National Bank-Vernon, 5/19/1976; Names: Alma S. Skipper| Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.507)
  - Claire D. Price, Vernon National Bank-Vernon, 5/19/1976; Names: Claire D. Price| Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.508)
  - Neal Landers Vo-Ag Program Director-RHS-Vernon, 6/4/1976; Names: Neal Landers| Topics: Schools & Education (Box 4, Folder MH.509)
  - Jeffrey P. Davidson Profiles Inc-Vernon, 6/15/1976; Names: Jeffrey P. Davidson| Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.510)
  - Jeffrey S. Graham, Harvest Hill Package Store-Rockville, 6/15/1976; Names: Jeffrey S. Graham (Box 4, Folder MH.511)
  - Mrs. Dorothy Miller,GOP Candidate for Assembly seat-55th Assembly District, 6/21/1976; Names: Dorothy Miller| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.512)
  - Rev. Eugene F. Mitchell-pastor of First Luth-Rockville, 07/??/76; Names: Eugene F. Mitchell| Topics: Churches (Box 4, Folder MH.513)
  - Dr. Jerome Lahman-office 57 Union St-Rockville, 7/2/1976; Names: Jerome Lahman| Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.514)
  - James Coleman, Connecticut Bank & Trust-Vernon, 7/7/1976; Names: James Coleman| Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.515)
  - Rockville Center from roof of East Street School-Rockville, 8/1/1976; Topics: Landmarks (Box 4, Folder MH.516)
  - John F. Perry ,1 Daryl Dr, LaBonne Agency-Vernon, 8/18/1976; Names: John F. Perry| Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.517)
  - Cheerleader Silhouette, 8/20/1976; Topics: Recreation (Box 4, Folder MH.518)
  - Leonard H. Mathiasen-Hartford National Bank & Trust-Vernon, 09/??/76; Names: Leonard H. Mathiasen| Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.519)
  - Chester Morgan-Vernon, 9/30/1976; Names: Chester Morgan| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.520)
  - Nancy Von Hone-Vernon, 9/23/1976; Names: Nancy Von Hone (Box 4, Folder MH.521)
  - Leslie Szalontai, Rainbow Advisor-Vernon, 9/30/1976; Names: Leslie Szalontai| Topics: Social Organizations (Box 4, Folder MH.522)
  - Mrs. Agnes Kerr-Rockville, 10/6/1976; Names: Mrs. Agnes Kerr (Box 4, Folder MH.523)
  - Mrs. Lois Tonski-Vernon, 11/1/1976; Names: Mrs. Lois Tonski (Box 4, Folder MH.524)
  - Barbara Jean Bousquet-Miss Junior Miss of Vernon for 1977, 11/8/1976; Names: Barbara Jean Bousquet| Topics: Social Organizations (Box 4, Folder MH.525)
  - Dr. Marshall A. Atwater-Vernon, 11/8/1976; Names: Marshall A. Atwater (Box 4, Folder MH.526)
  - Rev James R. Smith-Vernon, 11/9/1976; Names: James R. Smith| Topics: Churches (Box 4, Folder MH.527)
  - Rev S. Wayne Shaneyfelt-Vernon, 11/16/1976; Names: S. Wayne Shaneyfelt| Topics: Churches (Box 4, Folder MH.528)
  - Trip to Mansfield-singing at the Mansfield Training Ctr, 12/??/76; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 4, Folder MH.529)
  - William Lee-100 years old-Vernon, ??/??/77; Names: William Lee (Box 4, Folder MH.530)
  - Talcottville Fair Clown-Talcottville, ??/??/77; Topics: Talcottville (Box 4, Folder MH.531)
  - View From Henry Park-Rockville, 1/7/1977; Topics: Rockville Redevelopment; Landmarks (Box 4, Folder MH.532)
  - Vernon Charter Revision Comm 1st meeting-Vernon, 1/13/1977; Topics: Town Government (Box 4, Folder MH.533)
  - Diamond Showcase advertisement-Vernon, 1/14/1977; Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.534)
  - Demolition of old apartment building-Rockville, 1/15/1977; Topics: Rockville Redevelopment (Box 4, Folder MH.535)
  - Ed Jordan's Carpets-Advertisement-Vernon, 1/18/1977; Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.536)
  - Vernon Jaycees-Distinguished Service Award-Vernon, 1/20/1977; Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 4, Folder MH.537)
  - Snowblower-John Jzyk-Lake Street-Vernon, 2/7/1977; Names: John Jzyk (Box 4, Folder MH.538)
  - Hockanum Day Care Center (puppet show)-Rockville, 2/10/1977; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 4, Folder MH.539)
  - RGH Jack McElvein & Loretta McCombe-Rockville, 2/15/1977; Names: Jack McElvein & Loretta McCombe| Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 4, Folder MH.540)
  - Welles Country Village-Model-Talcottville, 2/28/1977; Topics: Housing; Talcottville (Box 4, Folder MH.541)
  - Welles Country Village-Floor Plan-Talcottville, 2/28/1977; Topics: Housing; Talcottville (Box 4, Folder MH.542)
  - Measles Clinic-Vernon, 3/1/1977; Topics: Public Health (Box 4, Folder MH.543)
  - New Fire Truck-Rockville, 3/2/1977; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 4, Folder MH.544)
  - Chinese New Year at Rockville Hospital-Rockville, 3/5/1977; Topics: Rockville Hospital; Holidays (Box 4, Folder MH.545)
  - Accident-Rt 83-Vernon, 3/5/1977; Topics: Police Dept. (Box 4, Folder MH.546)
  - Miss Tolland County Pagent-Vernon, 3/7/1977; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 4, Folder MH.547)
  - Women's Club gives TV to Rockville Hospital, 3/16/1977; Topics: Rockville Hospital; Social Organizations (Box 4, Folder MH.548)
  - Leslie Szalontai engaged-not Known, 3/16/1977; Names: Leslie Szalontai| Topics: Marriage & Family (Box 4, Folder MH.549)
  - Rockville Chamber of Comm-Products Show-Rockville, 3/21/1977; Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.550)
  - Mayor Tom Benoit & Youth Dir. Allen Richmond-Vernon, 4/4/1977; Names: Tom Benoit & Allen Richmond| Topics: Town Government (Box 4, Folder MH.551)
  - Meal carriers made by RHS Student-Rockville, 4/4/1977; Topics: RHS (Box 4, Folder MH.552)
  - House fire on Lake Street-Vernon, 4/5/1977; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 4, Folder MH.553)
  - Kids fall in puddles-Vernon, 4/6/1977; Topics: Entertainment (Box 4, Folder MH.554)
  - RHS seniors get scholarships:Barry Taylor (l) & Robert Kukulka-Rockville, 4/8/1977; Names: Barry Taylor & Robert Kukulka| Topics: RHS (Box 4, Folder MH.555)
  - Easter lilies at Union Cong Church-Rockville, 4/9/1977; Topics: Churches (Box 4, Folder MH.556)
  - Rabbit Run race-Rockville, 4/11/1977; Topics: Recreation (Box 4, Folder MH.557)
  - Judi Genovesi(l)cited for skating by State Reps Dorothy Miller & Chester Morgan, 4/13/1977; Names: Judi Genovesi| Topics: Politics & Elections; Recreation (Box 4, Folder MH.558)
  - Fishing Derby at Valley Falls Park, 4/18/1977; Topics: Recreation (Box 4, Folder MH.559)
  - Clown Town-Vernon, 4/26/1977; Topics: Recreation; Social Organizations (Box 4, Folder MH.560)
  - Civil War projects at Middle School-Vernon, 4/28/1977; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 4, Folder MH.561)
  - Post Office Sign-Rockville, 4/28/1977; Topics: Landmarks (Box 4, Folder MH.562)
  - Mayor tours Camp Newhoca-Vernon, 05/??/77; Topics: Recreation (Box 4, Folder MH.563)
  - Worths opens new store at TriCity Plaza-Vernon, 5/6/1977; Topics: Businesses; Vernon Circle (Box 4, Folder MH.564)
  - Easter Seals Bike Hike-Vernon, 5/17/1977; Topics: Recreation; Social Organizations (Box 4, Folder MH.565)
  - Metric Workshop at Northeast School-Rockville, 5/18/1977; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 4, Folder MH.566)
  - Mrs. Grace Hansen,Pres Rockville Emblem Club-Rockville, 5/20/1977; Names: Grace Hansen| Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 4, Folder MH.567)
  - JoAnn Worthen, Vernon Board of Ed-Vernon, 5/20/1977; Names: JoAnn Worthen (Box 4, Folder MH.568)
  - Vernon Elementary School-Field Day-Vernon, 5/26/1977; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 4, Folder MH.569)
  - Laser lecture at Middle School-Vernon, 5/26/1977; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 4, Folder MH.570)
  - Memorial Day Parade-Vernon, 5/30/1977; Topics: Holidays (Box 4, Folder MH.571)
  - Gov. Ella Grasso signs Praying Mantis bill-Vernon, 5/31/1977; Names: Ella Grasso| Topics: Schools & Education (Box 4, Folder MH.572)
  - Girls Athletic Club banquet at RHS-Rockville, 6/9/1977; Topics: Schools & Education; Recreation (Box 4, Folder MH.573)
  - Student Government Day with Mayor-Vernon, 6/10/1977; Topics: Schools & Education; Town Government (Box 4, Folder MH.574)
  - God & Country Award to Boy Scout at Talcottville Church-Talcottville, 6/15/1977; Topics: Civic Organizations; Churches; Talcottville (Box 4, Folder MH.575)
  - Diamond Showcase-Vernon, 6/18/1977; Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.576)
  - Mock disaster drill-Vernon, 6/27/1977; Topics: Schools & Education; Police Dept. (Box 4, Folder MH.577)
  - High School Graduation-Rockville, 6/28/1977; Topics: RHS (Box 4, Folder MH.578)
  - Swimming at Vernon Elementary pool, 7/9/1977; Topics: Recreation (Box 4, Folder MH.579)
  - Puppet workshop at Library-Rockville, 7/16/1977; Topics: Rockville Library (Box 4, Folder MH.580)
  - Clown & puppet show at CT Golfland-Talcottville, 7/28/1977; Topics: Recreation; Entertainment; Talcottville (Box 4, Folder MH.581)
  - St. Joseph Church Carnival-Rockville, 8/17/1977; Topics: Churches; Entertainment (Box 4, Folder MH.582)
  - HiFi Stereo House opens-Vernon, 8/5/1977; Topics: Businesses (Box 4, Folder MH.583)
  - Algae problem at Bolton Lake-Vernon, 8/10/1977; Topics: Parks; Environment (Box 4, Folder MH.584)
  - Vernon Cong Church Daycare 5th Birthday Party-Vernon, 8/13/1977; Topics: Churches (Box 4, Folder MH.585)
  - Getting ready for 4-H Fair-Vernon, 8/18/1977; Topics: Recreation; Farming (Box 4, Folder MH.586)
  - Fox Hill Tower clean up-Rockville, 8/19/1977; Topics: Parks; Landmarks (Box 4, Folder MH.587)
  - Mayor's Day at Henry Park-Rockville, 8/19/1977; Topics: Recreation; Town Government; Parks (Box 4, Folder MH.588)
  - Rockville Library program-Peter Rabbit's Birthday-Rockville, 8/25/1977; Topics: Rockville Library; Entertainment (Box B0x 4, Folder MH.589)
  - Rockville Library Mime Performance-Rockville, 8/25/1977; Topics: Rockville Library (Box 4, Folder MH.590)
  - Removing junk cars from Paper Mill Pond-Rockville, 8/26/1977; Topics: Environment (Box 4, Folder MH.591)
  - Tolland County Antique Market-Vernon, 8/29/1977; Topics: Businesses; Entertainment (Box 4, Folder MH.592)
  - TriTown Players' "Plaza Suite" auditions-Vernon, 8/31/1977; Topics: Entertainment (Box 4, Folder MH.593)
  - Mayor Tom Benoit on horse-Vernon, 09/??/77; Names: Tom Benoit (Box 4, Folder MH.594)
  - Kids "jump falls" Talcottville, 09/??/77; Topics: Entertainment; Talcottville (Box 4, Folder MH.595)
  - Mrs. Bruce Cramer with Mayor Tom Benoit-Vernon, 9/3/1977; Names: Mrs. Bruce Cramer & Tom Benoit (Box 4, Folder MH.596)
  - Bolton Rd-I-86 Construction-Vernon, 9/3/1977; Topics: Transportation (Box 4, Folder MH.597)
  - Fire Explorers selling big comic books-Vernon, 9/6/1977; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 4, Folder MH.598)
  - Kids at Rockville Library for Sat. question feature, 9/10/1977; Topics: Rockville Library (Box 4, Folder MH.599)
  - Lake St School studies butterflies-Vernon, 9/15/1977; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 4, Folder MH.600)
  - Mayor Tom Benoit with Cub Scouts-Vernon, 9/20/1977; Names: Tom Benoit| Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 4, Folder MH.601)
  - New Pastor at Vernon Meth Church-Vernon, 9/20/1977; Topics: Churches (Box 4, Folder MH.602)
  - Boys play football on Bolton Rd-Vernon, 9/23/1977; Topics: Recreation (Box 4, Folder MH.603)
  - Narrow Bolton Road-Vernon, 9/23/1977; Topics: Transportation (Box 4, Folder MH.604)
  - I-86 Construction-Vernon, 9/23/1977; Topics: Transportation (Box 4, Folder MH.605)
  - 3yr old construction worker on Rt 83-Vernon, 9/30/1977; Topics: Transportation (Box 4, Folder MH.606)
  - New sewage treatment plant-Vernon, 9/30/1977; Topics: Public Health; Environment (Box 4, Folder MH.607)
  - Ground breaking for new police station-Vernon (2nd from left-Cong. Chris Dodd), 10/??/77; Names: Chris Dodd| Topics: Police Dept. (Box 4, Folder MH.608)
  - Carl Anderson, Vernon Candidate-Vernon, 10/??/77; Names: Carl Anderson| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.609)
  - Harold Cummings-political candidate-Vernon, 10/??/77; Names: Harold Cummings| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.610)
  - Joy DiPietro-Candidate-Vernon, 10/??/77; Names: Joy DiPietro| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.611)
  - Robert DuBeau-candidate-Vernon, 10/??/77; Names: Robert DuBeau| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.612)
  - Frank McCoy-Vernon, 10/??/77; Names: Frank McCoy| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.613)
  - Steven Marcham-Vernon, 10/??/77; Names: Steven Marcham| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.614)
  - John Giulette, candidate-Vernon, 10/??/77; Names: John Giulette| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.615)
  - Robert Ramejko, candidate-Vernon, 10/??/77; Names: Robert Ramejko| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.616)
  - George Prouty, Sr. candidate-Vernon, 10/??/77; Names: George Prouty, Sr.| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.617)
  - Robert Wehrli-Vernon, 10/??/77; Names: Robert Wehrli| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.618)
  - Lena Therault, candidate-Vernon, 10/??/77; Names: Lena Therault| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.619)
  - M. Russell McPadden, candidate-Vernon, 10/??/77; Names: M. Russell McPadden| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.620)
  - Joseph Merluzzo, candidate-Vernon, 10/??/77; Names: Joseph Merluzzo| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.621)
  - Mary Mott, candidate-Vernon, 10/??/77; Names: Mary Mott| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.622)
  - Marian Narkowicz incumbent selectman-Vernon, 10/??/77; Names: Marian Narkowicz| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.623)
  - Theodore Ventura,selectman-Vernon, 10/??/77; Names: Theodore Ventura| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.624)
  - Democratic Headquarters open-Vernon, 10/11/1977; Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.625)